Guide to the Records of the History Department of the Faculty of Arts and Science 1926-1978 (Bulk 1960-1970) RG 21.3 RG 21.3
New York University Archives
- Series I: Administrative Records
  - Light, Dale B., Jr., undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Long, Robert E, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - McEvoy, Arthur F., undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Oakes, James, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Pritchard, Linda K., undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Shephard, Rebecca, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Siracusa, Carl F, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Wright, Mary C., undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Zimmerman, Joan Grace, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD-Oct, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Oct, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Oct, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Oct, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Oct, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Oct, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Oct, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Oct, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226365 0
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Oct, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Oct, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Oct, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Fall, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- April, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Qualifying Examinations, PhD- Fall, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Office of the Dean, 1928-1934 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Office of the Dean, 1934-1937 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Office of the Dean, 1938-1941 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - AB Dean's Office, 1942-1946 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - (Registration) Advisory Council, 1938-1941 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Advisement, 1934-1937 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Advisement, 1929-1934 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Freshmen Advisory Committee, 1926-1941 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Advisement Folder, 1926-1941 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - MA and PhD Examinations, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - History Dept WSC, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - History Dept, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - History House- Heights, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Enrollment Figures in History, 1947-1951 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Vugrinecz- Prof Prince, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 25)